

LISANDRO BIGI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hello! I'm a Front-End Developer (Full in Stack training) and Anthropologist. With professional experience in various projects (+4 years), I am proficient in: React.js Vue.js | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | Node.js | Next.js | Nuxt.js | Git | Wordpress.

My interests lie in Web Development, Responsive and Adaptive Web Design, User Interfaces (UI), User Experience (UX), Front-End Development, Web3, APIs, Full-Stack Development, and Web Design.

CONTACT

+54 9 351 631 9690

bigilisandro@gmail.com

Córdoba, Argentina

SKILLS



















EXPERIENCE

YERBO, Full Stack Engineer (AUG 2023 - PRESENT)

I played a key role in creating a new impactful platform designed for trainers to showcase, measure, and enhance their training programs. Our primary tech stack includes React.js and Node.js,

INCLUIT, React Developer (JUN 2022 - JUL 2023)

I contributed to the development of a UCMS software platform designed for efficiently managing court cases within the state of Texas, United States. My responsibilities primarily involved utilizing React for the front-end development of the web application.

KICKSTA, Front-End Developer (MAY 2021 - JUN 2022)

I primarily contributed to the development of their flagship product, Kicksta, along with other web applications like InfluenceGrid and Wedding Hashers. The key technologies utilized in these projects included Vue.js and Nuxt.js.

PENGYI, Front-End Developer (JUN 2019 - JUL 2021) In this software company, I was engaging in projects primarily utilizing Vue.js and React for a diverse clientele worldwide. Additionally, I gained experience working with JavaScript, TypeScript and Node.js technologies.

EDUCATION

EDUCATIONIT, Blockchain Ethereum Solidity MAY 2022 - AGO 2022

VUE MASTERY, Vue.js Learning Platform DEC 2020 - DEC 2021

CODERHOUSE, React.js

FFB 2020 - JUN 2020

ACAMICA, Full Stack Web Development

NOV 2019 - JUN 2020

CODERHOUSE, UX/UI Design

MAY 2020 - SFP 2020

FFyH - UNC, Anthropology Degree

FEB 2013 - MAR 2020

CODERHOUSE, Web Designer

OCT 2019 - DIC 2019



